[{"subjectID":"dgfpp7mm9a","prolificID":"6727c740ea8634fcd0f43ebd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25a36f66e5169a570f0","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980731496,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":0,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"74","question":"What’s a smell or sound that most people find unappealing but that you actually like?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":42,"rt":72713,"timeElapsed":343591},{"subjectID":"dgfpp7mm9a","prolificID":"6727c740ea8634fcd0f43ebd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25a36f66e5169a570f0","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980747257,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":1,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"74","question":"What’s a smell or sound that most people find unappealing but that you actually like?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":40,"rt":15755,"timeElapsed":359352},{"subjectID":"dgfpp7mm9a","prolificID":"6727c740ea8634fcd0f43ebd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25a36f66e5169a570f0","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980783976,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":2,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"74","question":"What’s a smell or sound that most people find unappealing but that you actually like?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":62,"rt":36713,"timeElapsed":396071},{"subjectID":"dgfpp7mm9a","prolificID":"6727c740ea8634fcd0f43ebd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25a36f66e5169a570f0","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980812218,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":3,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"74","question":"What’s a smell or sound that most people find unappealing but that you actually like?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":45,"rt":28237,"timeElapsed":424313},{"subjectID":"dgfpp7mm9a","prolificID":"6727c740ea8634fcd0f43ebd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25a36f66e5169a570f0","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980840154,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":4,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"74","question":"What’s a smell or sound that most people find unappealing but that you actually like?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":72,"rt":27930,"timeElapsed":452248},{"subjectID":"dgfpp7mm9a","prolificID":"6727c740ea8634fcd0f43ebd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25a36f66e5169a570f0","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980848661,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":5,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"74","question":"What’s a smell or sound that most people find unappealing but that you actually like?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":62,"rt":8503,"timeElapsed":460756},{"subjectID":"dgfpp7mm9a","prolificID":"6727c740ea8634fcd0f43ebd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25a36f66e5169a570f0","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980861106,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":6,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"74","question":"What’s a smell or sound that most people find unappealing but that you actually like?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":65,"rt":12440,"timeElapsed":473201},{"subjectID":"dgfpp7mm9a","prolificID":"6727c740ea8634fcd0f43ebd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25a36f66e5169a570f0","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980923481,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":7,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"74","question":"What’s a smell or sound that most people find unappealing but that you actually like?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":59,"rt":62369,"timeElapsed":535576},{"subjectID":"dgfpp7mm9a","prolificID":"6727c740ea8634fcd0f43ebd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25a36f66e5169a570f0","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980940926,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":8,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"74","question":"What’s a smell or sound that most people find unappealing but that you actually like?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":56,"rt":17441,"timeElapsed":553021},{"subjectID":"dgfpp7mm9a","prolificID":"6727c740ea8634fcd0f43ebd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25a36f66e5169a570f0","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980958189,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":9,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"195","question":"Did you play any sports growing up? If multiple, which was your favorite? Do you still play?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":44,"rt":7975,"timeElapsed":570284},{"subjectID":"dgfpp7mm9a","prolificID":"6727c740ea8634fcd0f43ebd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25a36f66e5169a570f0","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980963535,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":10,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"195","question":"Did you play any sports growing up? If multiple, which was your favorite? Do you still play?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":57,"rt":5341,"timeElapsed":575630},{"subjectID":"dgfpp7mm9a","prolificID":"6727c740ea8634fcd0f43ebd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25a36f66e5169a570f0","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980978453,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":11,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"195","question":"Did you play any sports growing up? If multiple, which was your favorite? Do you still play?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":56,"rt":14913,"timeElapsed":590548},{"subjectID":"dgfpp7mm9a","prolificID":"6727c740ea8634fcd0f43ebd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25a36f66e5169a570f0","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981010496,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":12,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"195","question":"Did you play any sports growing up? If multiple, which was your favorite? Do you still play?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":55,"rt":32038,"timeElapsed":622590},{"subjectID":"dgfpp7mm9a","prolificID":"6727c740ea8634fcd0f43ebd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25a36f66e5169a570f0","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981022292,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":13,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"195","question":"Did you play any sports growing up? If multiple, which was your favorite? Do you still play?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":54,"rt":11792,"timeElapsed":634387},{"subjectID":"dgfpp7mm9a","prolificID":"6727c740ea8634fcd0f43ebd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25a36f66e5169a570f0","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981032018,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":14,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"195","question":"Did you play any sports growing up? If multiple, which was your favorite? Do you still play?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":57,"rt":9721,"timeElapsed":644113},{"subjectID":"dgfpp7mm9a","prolificID":"6727c740ea8634fcd0f43ebd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25a36f66e5169a570f0","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981060695,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":15,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"195","question":"Did you play any sports growing up? If multiple, which was your favorite? Do you still play?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":55,"rt":28673,"timeElapsed":672789},{"subjectID":"dgfpp7mm9a","prolificID":"6727c740ea8634fcd0f43ebd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25a36f66e5169a570f0","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981083613,"comprehensionCheck":1,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":0,"trialIdx":15,"questionIdx":null,"scaleIdx":null,"questionID":null,"question":"Did you play any sports growing up? If multiple, which was your favorite? Do you still play?","questionCategory":"comprehension check","scaleID":null,"scaleBlock":null,"scaleText":"Please drag the slider all the way to the end labeled STRAWBERRY","scaleTextMin":"STRAWBERRY","scaleTextMax":"PINEAPPLE","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":22915,"timeElapsed":695708},{"subjectID":"dgfpp7mm9a","prolificID":"6727c740ea8634fcd0f43ebd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25a36f66e5169a570f0","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981103844,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":16,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"195","question":"Did you play any sports growing up? If multiple, which was your favorite? Do you still play?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":56,"rt":20226,"timeElapsed":715939},{"subjectID":"dgfpp7mm9a","prolificID":"6727c740ea8634fcd0f43ebd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25a36f66e5169a570f0","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981110976,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":17,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"195","question":"Did you play any sports growing up? If multiple, which was your favorite? Do you still play?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":53,"rt":7129,"timeElapsed":723071},{"subjectID":"dgfpp7mm9a","prolificID":"6727c740ea8634fcd0f43ebd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25a36f66e5169a570f0","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981166110,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":18,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"30","question":"If you were to die this evening with no opportunity to communicate with anyone, what would you most regret not having told someone? Why haven’t you told them yet?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":60,"rt":52230,"timeElapsed":778205},{"subjectID":"dgfpp7mm9a","prolificID":"6727c740ea8634fcd0f43ebd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25a36f66e5169a570f0","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981234749,"comprehensionCheck":1,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":100,"trialIdx":18,"questionIdx":null,"scaleIdx":null,"questionID":null,"question":"If you were to die this evening with no opportunity to communicate with anyone, what would you most regret not having told someone? Why haven’t you told them yet?","questionCategory":"comprehension check","scaleID":null,"scaleBlock":null,"scaleText":"Please drag the slider all the way to the end labeled HAMBURGER","scaleTextMin":"HOTDOG","scaleTextMax":"HAMBURGER","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":68635,"timeElapsed":846844},{"subjectID":"dgfpp7mm9a","prolificID":"6727c740ea8634fcd0f43ebd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25a36f66e5169a570f0","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981249058,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":19,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"30","question":"If you were to die this evening with no opportunity to communicate with anyone, what would you most regret not having told someone? Why haven’t you told them yet?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":54,"rt":14304,"timeElapsed":861153},{"subjectID":"dgfpp7mm9a","prolificID":"6727c740ea8634fcd0f43ebd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25a36f66e5169a570f0","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981256417,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":20,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"30","question":"If you were to die this evening with no opportunity to communicate with anyone, what would you most regret not having told someone? Why haven’t you told them yet?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":55,"rt":7355,"timeElapsed":868512},{"subjectID":"dgfpp7mm9a","prolificID":"6727c740ea8634fcd0f43ebd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25a36f66e5169a570f0","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981263928,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":21,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"30","question":"If you were to die this evening with no opportunity to communicate with anyone, what would you most regret not having told someone? Why haven’t you told them yet?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":55,"rt":7507,"timeElapsed":876023},{"subjectID":"dgfpp7mm9a","prolificID":"6727c740ea8634fcd0f43ebd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25a36f66e5169a570f0","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981283868,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":22,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"30","question":"If you were to die this evening with no opportunity to communicate with anyone, what would you most regret not having told someone? Why haven’t you told them yet?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":55,"rt":19935,"timeElapsed":895963},{"subjectID":"dgfpp7mm9a","prolificID":"6727c740ea8634fcd0f43ebd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25a36f66e5169a570f0","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981303250,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":23,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"30","question":"If you were to die this evening with no opportunity to communicate with anyone, what would you most regret not having told someone? Why haven’t you told them yet?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":56,"rt":19378,"timeElapsed":915345},{"subjectID":"dgfpp7mm9a","prolificID":"6727c740ea8634fcd0f43ebd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25a36f66e5169a570f0","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981317998,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":24,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"30","question":"If you were to die this evening with no opportunity to communicate with anyone, what would you most regret not having told someone? Why haven’t you told them yet?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":58,"rt":14744,"timeElapsed":930093},{"subjectID":"dgfpp7mm9a","prolificID":"6727c740ea8634fcd0f43ebd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25a36f66e5169a570f0","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981325767,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":25,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"30","question":"If you were to die this evening with no opportunity to communicate with anyone, what would you most regret not having told someone? Why haven’t you told them yet?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":57,"rt":7764,"timeElapsed":937862},{"subjectID":"dgfpp7mm9a","prolificID":"6727c740ea8634fcd0f43ebd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25a36f66e5169a570f0","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981332360,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":26,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"30","question":"If you were to die this evening with no opportunity to communicate with anyone, what would you most regret not having told someone? Why haven’t you told them yet?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":59,"rt":6590,"timeElapsed":944455},{"subjectID":"dgfpp7mm9a","prolificID":"6727c740ea8634fcd0f43ebd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25a36f66e5169a570f0","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981343399,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":27,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"163","question":"Did you have a class pet when you were in elementary school? Do you remember the pet’s name? What kind of animal was it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":58,"rt":6357,"timeElapsed":955494},{"subjectID":"dgfpp7mm9a","prolificID":"6727c740ea8634fcd0f43ebd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25a36f66e5169a570f0","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981347849,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":28,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"163","question":"Did you have a class pet when you were in elementary school? Do you remember the pet’s name? What kind of animal was it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":59,"rt":4445,"timeElapsed":959944},{"subjectID":"dgfpp7mm9a","prolificID":"6727c740ea8634fcd0f43ebd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25a36f66e5169a570f0","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981353962,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":29,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"163","question":"Did you have a class pet when you were in elementary school? Do you remember the pet’s name? What kind of animal was it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":58,"rt":6109,"timeElapsed":966057},{"subjectID":"dgfpp7mm9a","prolificID":"6727c740ea8634fcd0f43ebd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25a36f66e5169a570f0","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981373535,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":30,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"163","question":"Did you have a class pet when you were in elementary school? Do you remember the pet’s name? What kind of animal was it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":57,"rt":19568,"timeElapsed":985630},{"subjectID":"dgfpp7mm9a","prolificID":"6727c740ea8634fcd0f43ebd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25a36f66e5169a570f0","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981380281,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":31,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"163","question":"Did you have a class pet when you were in elementary school? Do you remember the pet’s name? What kind of animal was it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":58,"rt":6743,"timeElapsed":992376},{"subjectID":"dgfpp7mm9a","prolificID":"6727c740ea8634fcd0f43ebd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25a36f66e5169a570f0","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981387592,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":32,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"163","question":"Did you have a class pet when you were in elementary school? Do you remember the pet’s name? What kind of animal was it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":58,"rt":7307,"timeElapsed":999687},{"subjectID":"dgfpp7mm9a","prolificID":"6727c740ea8634fcd0f43ebd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25a36f66e5169a570f0","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981425621,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":33,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"163","question":"Did you have a class pet when you were in elementary school? Do you remember the pet’s name? What kind of animal was it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":57,"rt":38025,"timeElapsed":1037716},{"subjectID":"dgfpp7mm9a","prolificID":"6727c740ea8634fcd0f43ebd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25a36f66e5169a570f0","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981456848,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":34,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"163","question":"Did you have a class pet when you were in elementary school? Do you remember the pet’s name? What kind of animal was it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":53,"rt":31223,"timeElapsed":1068943},{"subjectID":"dgfpp7mm9a","prolificID":"6727c740ea8634fcd0f43ebd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25a36f66e5169a570f0","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981472469,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":35,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"163","question":"Did you have a class pet when you were in elementary school? Do you remember the pet’s name? What kind of animal was it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":56,"rt":15616,"timeElapsed":1084564},{"subjectID":"dgfpp7mm9a","prolificID":"6727c740ea8634fcd0f43ebd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25a36f66e5169a570f0","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981488036,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":36,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"226","question":"If you had to train an animal to perform in a circus or other show, what animal would you train and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":57,"rt":7536,"timeElapsed":1100131},{"subjectID":"dgfpp7mm9a","prolificID":"6727c740ea8634fcd0f43ebd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25a36f66e5169a570f0","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981500241,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":37,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"226","question":"If you had to train an animal to perform in a circus or other show, what animal would you train and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":56,"rt":12201,"timeElapsed":1112336},{"subjectID":"dgfpp7mm9a","prolificID":"6727c740ea8634fcd0f43ebd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25a36f66e5169a570f0","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981504106,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":38,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"226","question":"If you had to train an animal to perform in a circus or other show, what animal would you train and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":56,"rt":3861,"timeElapsed":1116200},{"subjectID":"dgfpp7mm9a","prolificID":"6727c740ea8634fcd0f43ebd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25a36f66e5169a570f0","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981510047,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":39,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"226","question":"If you had to train an animal to perform in a circus or other show, what animal would you train and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":55,"rt":5938,"timeElapsed":1122142},{"subjectID":"dgfpp7mm9a","prolificID":"6727c740ea8634fcd0f43ebd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25a36f66e5169a570f0","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981515695,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":40,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"226","question":"If you had to train an animal to perform in a circus or other show, what animal would you train and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":54,"rt":5644,"timeElapsed":1127790},{"subjectID":"dgfpp7mm9a","prolificID":"6727c740ea8634fcd0f43ebd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25a36f66e5169a570f0","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981529789,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":41,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"226","question":"If you had to train an animal to perform in a circus or other show, what animal would you train and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":55,"rt":14090,"timeElapsed":1141884},{"subjectID":"dgfpp7mm9a","prolificID":"6727c740ea8634fcd0f43ebd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25a36f66e5169a570f0","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981542652,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":42,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"226","question":"If you had to train an animal to perform in a circus or other show, what animal would you train and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":55,"rt":12859,"timeElapsed":1154747},{"subjectID":"dgfpp7mm9a","prolificID":"6727c740ea8634fcd0f43ebd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25a36f66e5169a570f0","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981563046,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":43,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"226","question":"If you had to train an animal to perform in a circus or other show, what animal would you train and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":54,"rt":20390,"timeElapsed":1175141},{"subjectID":"dgfpp7mm9a","prolificID":"6727c740ea8634fcd0f43ebd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25a36f66e5169a570f0","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981567905,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":44,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"226","question":"If you had to train an animal to perform in a circus or other show, what animal would you train and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":56,"rt":4855,"timeElapsed":1180000},{"subjectID":"dgfpp7mm9a","prolificID":"6727c740ea8634fcd0f43ebd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25a36f66e5169a570f0","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981576931,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":45,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"159","question":"What is the best book you have read or started in the last three months? Describe it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":56,"rt":6121,"timeElapsed":1189026},{"subjectID":"dgfpp7mm9a","prolificID":"6727c740ea8634fcd0f43ebd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25a36f66e5169a570f0","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981581784,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":46,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"159","question":"What is the best book you have read or started in the last three months? Describe it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":54,"rt":4849,"timeElapsed":1193879},{"subjectID":"dgfpp7mm9a","prolificID":"6727c740ea8634fcd0f43ebd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25a36f66e5169a570f0","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981588528,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":47,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"159","question":"What is the best book you have read or started in the last three months? Describe it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":54,"rt":6740,"timeElapsed":1200623},{"subjectID":"dgfpp7mm9a","prolificID":"6727c740ea8634fcd0f43ebd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25a36f66e5169a570f0","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981596547,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":48,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"159","question":"What is the best book you have read or started in the last three months? Describe it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":54,"rt":8015,"timeElapsed":1208642},{"subjectID":"dgfpp7mm9a","prolificID":"6727c740ea8634fcd0f43ebd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25a36f66e5169a570f0","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981603156,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":49,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"159","question":"What is the best book you have read or started in the last three months? Describe it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":54,"rt":6605,"timeElapsed":1215250},{"subjectID":"dgfpp7mm9a","prolificID":"6727c740ea8634fcd0f43ebd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25a36f66e5169a570f0","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981608430,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":50,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"159","question":"What is the best book you have read or started in the last three months? Describe it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":54,"rt":5271,"timeElapsed":1220525},{"subjectID":"dgfpp7mm9a","prolificID":"6727c740ea8634fcd0f43ebd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25a36f66e5169a570f0","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981615636,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":51,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"159","question":"What is the best book you have read or started in the last three months? Describe it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":54,"rt":7201,"timeElapsed":1227731},{"subjectID":"dgfpp7mm9a","prolificID":"6727c740ea8634fcd0f43ebd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25a36f66e5169a570f0","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981631701,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":52,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"159","question":"What is the best book you have read or started in the last three months? Describe it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":54,"rt":16061,"timeElapsed":1243796},{"subjectID":"dgfpp7mm9a","prolificID":"6727c740ea8634fcd0f43ebd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25a36f66e5169a570f0","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981637651,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":53,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"159","question":"What is the best book you have read or started in the last three months? Describe it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":54,"rt":5946,"timeElapsed":1249746},{"subjectID":"dgfpp7mm9a","prolificID":"6727c740ea8634fcd0f43ebd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25a36f66e5169a570f0","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981645502,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":54,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"36","question":"Describe a time you felt most full of joy.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":55,"rt":5356,"timeElapsed":1257597},{"subjectID":"dgfpp7mm9a","prolificID":"6727c740ea8634fcd0f43ebd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25a36f66e5169a570f0","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981651036,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":55,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"36","question":"Describe a time you felt most full of joy.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":54,"rt":5530,"timeElapsed":1263131},{"subjectID":"dgfpp7mm9a","prolificID":"6727c740ea8634fcd0f43ebd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25a36f66e5169a570f0","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981657252,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":56,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"36","question":"Describe a time you felt most full of joy.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":54,"rt":6212,"timeElapsed":1269347},{"subjectID":"dgfpp7mm9a","prolificID":"6727c740ea8634fcd0f43ebd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25a36f66e5169a570f0","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981664418,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":57,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"36","question":"Describe a time you felt most full of joy.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":54,"rt":7161,"timeElapsed":1276513},{"subjectID":"dgfpp7mm9a","prolificID":"6727c740ea8634fcd0f43ebd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25a36f66e5169a570f0","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981670574,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":58,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"36","question":"Describe a time you felt most full of joy.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":54,"rt":6152,"timeElapsed":1282668},{"subjectID":"dgfpp7mm9a","prolificID":"6727c740ea8634fcd0f43ebd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25a36f66e5169a570f0","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981676533,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":59,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"36","question":"Describe a time you felt most full of joy.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":54,"rt":5954,"timeElapsed":1288628},{"subjectID":"dgfpp7mm9a","prolificID":"6727c740ea8634fcd0f43ebd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25a36f66e5169a570f0","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981688072,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":60,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"36","question":"Describe a time you felt most full of joy.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":54,"rt":11536,"timeElapsed":1300167},{"subjectID":"dgfpp7mm9a","prolificID":"6727c740ea8634fcd0f43ebd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25a36f66e5169a570f0","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981696891,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":61,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"36","question":"Describe a time you felt most full of joy.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":55,"rt":8815,"timeElapsed":1308986},{"subjectID":"dgfpp7mm9a","prolificID":"6727c740ea8634fcd0f43ebd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25a36f66e5169a570f0","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981705210,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":62,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"36","question":"Describe a time you felt most full of joy.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":53,"rt":8315,"timeElapsed":1317305},{"subjectID":"dgfpp7mm9a","prolificID":"6727c740ea8634fcd0f43ebd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25a36f66e5169a570f0","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981721564,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":63,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"181","question":"What is your earliest memory? Do you know how old you were in this memory?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":54,"rt":13697,"timeElapsed":1333659},{"subjectID":"dgfpp7mm9a","prolificID":"6727c740ea8634fcd0f43ebd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25a36f66e5169a570f0","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981730072,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":64,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"181","question":"What is your earliest memory? Do you know how old you were in this memory?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":54,"rt":8504,"timeElapsed":1342167},{"subjectID":"dgfpp7mm9a","prolificID":"6727c740ea8634fcd0f43ebd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25a36f66e5169a570f0","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981748736,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":65,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"181","question":"What is your earliest memory? Do you know how old you were in this memory?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":53,"rt":18659,"timeElapsed":1360830},{"subjectID":"dgfpp7mm9a","prolificID":"6727c740ea8634fcd0f43ebd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25a36f66e5169a570f0","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981755722,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":66,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"181","question":"What is your earliest memory? Do you know how old you were in this memory?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":53,"rt":6982,"timeElapsed":1367816},{"subjectID":"dgfpp7mm9a","prolificID":"6727c740ea8634fcd0f43ebd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25a36f66e5169a570f0","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981762812,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":67,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"181","question":"What is your earliest memory? Do you know how old you were in this memory?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":55,"rt":7086,"timeElapsed":1374907},{"subjectID":"dgfpp7mm9a","prolificID":"6727c740ea8634fcd0f43ebd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25a36f66e5169a570f0","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981768899,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":68,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"181","question":"What is your earliest memory? Do you know how old you were in this memory?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":54,"rt":6083,"timeElapsed":1380994},{"subjectID":"dgfpp7mm9a","prolificID":"6727c740ea8634fcd0f43ebd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25a36f66e5169a570f0","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981788804,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":69,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"181","question":"What is your earliest memory? Do you know how old you were in this memory?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":51,"rt":19901,"timeElapsed":1400899},{"subjectID":"dgfpp7mm9a","prolificID":"6727c740ea8634fcd0f43ebd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25a36f66e5169a570f0","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981796676,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":70,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"181","question":"What is your earliest memory? Do you know how old you were in this memory?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":56,"rt":7868,"timeElapsed":1408771},{"subjectID":"dgfpp7mm9a","prolificID":"6727c740ea8634fcd0f43ebd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25a36f66e5169a570f0","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981815919,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":71,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"181","question":"What is your earliest memory? Do you know how old you were in this memory?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":55,"rt":19239,"timeElapsed":1428014},{"subjectID":"dgfpp7mm9a","prolificID":"6727c740ea8634fcd0f43ebd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25a36f66e5169a570f0","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981844876,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":72,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"99","question":"Under what circumstances do you think you could kill someone, if any?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":55,"rt":11570,"timeElapsed":1456971},{"subjectID":"dgfpp7mm9a","prolificID":"6727c740ea8634fcd0f43ebd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25a36f66e5169a570f0","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981961572,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":73,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"99","question":"Under what circumstances do you think you could kill someone, if any?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":58,"rt":116692,"timeElapsed":1573667},{"subjectID":"dgfpp7mm9a","prolificID":"6727c740ea8634fcd0f43ebd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25a36f66e5169a570f0","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981972265,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":74,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"99","question":"Under what circumstances do you think you could kill someone, if any?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":54,"rt":10689,"timeElapsed":1584360},{"subjectID":"dgfpp7mm9a","prolificID":"6727c740ea8634fcd0f43ebd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25a36f66e5169a570f0","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981983290,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":75,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"99","question":"Under what circumstances do you think you could kill someone, if any?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":56,"rt":11020,"timeElapsed":1595385},{"subjectID":"dgfpp7mm9a","prolificID":"6727c740ea8634fcd0f43ebd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25a36f66e5169a570f0","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981992524,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":76,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"99","question":"Under what circumstances do you think you could kill someone, if any?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":55,"rt":9230,"timeElapsed":1604619},{"subjectID":"dgfpp7mm9a","prolificID":"6727c740ea8634fcd0f43ebd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25a36f66e5169a570f0","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981999164,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":77,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"99","question":"Under what circumstances do you think you could kill someone, if any?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":55,"rt":6635,"timeElapsed":1611259},{"subjectID":"dgfpp7mm9a","prolificID":"6727c740ea8634fcd0f43ebd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25a36f66e5169a570f0","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734982006509,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":78,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"99","question":"Under what circumstances do you think you could kill someone, if any?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":63,"rt":7341,"timeElapsed":1618604},{"subjectID":"dgfpp7mm9a","prolificID":"6727c740ea8634fcd0f43ebd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25a36f66e5169a570f0","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734982057700,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":79,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"99","question":"Under what circumstances do you think you could kill someone, if any?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":58,"rt":51186,"timeElapsed":1669795},{"subjectID":"dgfpp7mm9a","prolificID":"6727c740ea8634fcd0f43ebd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25a36f66e5169a570f0","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734982075562,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":80,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"99","question":"Under what circumstances do you think you could kill someone, if any?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":55,"rt":17858,"timeElapsed":1687657},{"subjectID":"dgfpp7mm9a","prolificID":"6727c740ea8634fcd0f43ebd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25a36f66e5169a570f0","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734982094954,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":81,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"59","question":"If you could live anywhere in the world irrespective of cost, where would it be and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":56,"rt":9935,"timeElapsed":1707049},{"subjectID":"dgfpp7mm9a","prolificID":"6727c740ea8634fcd0f43ebd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25a36f66e5169a570f0","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734982103682,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":82,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"59","question":"If you could live anywhere in the world irrespective of cost, where would it be and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":58,"rt":8723,"timeElapsed":1715777},{"subjectID":"dgfpp7mm9a","prolificID":"6727c740ea8634fcd0f43ebd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25a36f66e5169a570f0","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734982108320,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":83,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"59","question":"If you could live anywhere in the world irrespective of cost, where would it be and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":58,"rt":4634,"timeElapsed":1720415},{"subjectID":"dgfpp7mm9a","prolificID":"6727c740ea8634fcd0f43ebd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25a36f66e5169a570f0","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734982112607,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":84,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"59","question":"If you could live anywhere in the world irrespective of cost, where would it be and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":57,"rt":4283,"timeElapsed":1724702},{"subjectID":"dgfpp7mm9a","prolificID":"6727c740ea8634fcd0f43ebd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25a36f66e5169a570f0","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734982117447,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":85,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"59","question":"If you could live anywhere in the world irrespective of cost, where would it be and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":58,"rt":4836,"timeElapsed":1729542},{"subjectID":"dgfpp7mm9a","prolificID":"6727c740ea8634fcd0f43ebd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25a36f66e5169a570f0","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734982122427,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":86,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"59","question":"If you could live anywhere in the world irrespective of cost, where would it be and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":56,"rt":4976,"timeElapsed":1734522},{"subjectID":"dgfpp7mm9a","prolificID":"6727c740ea8634fcd0f43ebd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25a36f66e5169a570f0","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734982127425,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":87,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"59","question":"If you could live anywhere in the world irrespective of cost, where would it be and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":56,"rt":4993,"timeElapsed":1739520},{"subjectID":"dgfpp7mm9a","prolificID":"6727c740ea8634fcd0f43ebd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25a36f66e5169a570f0","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734982136715,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":88,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"59","question":"If you could live anywhere in the world irrespective of cost, where would it be and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":56,"rt":9286,"timeElapsed":1748810},{"subjectID":"dgfpp7mm9a","prolificID":"6727c740ea8634fcd0f43ebd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25a36f66e5169a570f0","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734982150329,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":89,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"59","question":"If you could live anywhere in the world irrespective of cost, where would it be and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":56,"rt":13609,"timeElapsed":1762424}]